{
    "subject": "resource/Martin_Hellman",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/New_York",
    "human_readable": "Martin Hellman was born in New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9090197682380676,
            "question": "Where was Martin Hellman born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6196553707122803,
            "question": "Is Martin Hellman an American citizen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4994838833808899,
            "question": "What is Martin Hellman known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43946149945259094,
            "question": "In what year did Martin Hellman live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3156602680683136,
            "question": "What are some notable achievements of people born in New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29785582423210144,
            "question": "What field is Martin Hellman associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2811320126056671,
            "question": "Are there any interesting facts about Martin Hellman's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2504349946975708,
            "question": "What significant contributions did Martin Hellman make to his field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1726771742105484,
            "question": "What impact did Martin Hellman's work have on the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1268233209848404,
            "question": "Who are some other prominent figures from New York?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Martin Hellman was born in New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7393_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Martin Hellman's work have on the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7393_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant contributions did Martin Hellman make to his field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7393_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any interesting facts about Martin Hellman's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7393_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7393_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7393_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7393_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7393_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7393_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7393_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7393_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7393_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7393_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7393_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms Martin Hellman was indeed born in New York City. This is explicitly stated in multiple documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7393/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7393/re-ranker-msmarco/44.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Martin E. Hellman, also referred to as simply Martin Hellman, was born on October 2, 1945, in New York City. Therefore, the statement \"Martin Hellman was born in New York\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}